citibank.com.sg 2013-05-22

# Citibank Privacy - Citibank Singapore

|  |  | Home>Privacy  
---  
  
| Privacy at Citi:  
---  
  
Our goal is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you.  
  
You have choices:  
  
As a Citi customer, you have the opportunity to make choices. As you consider this, we encourage you to make choices that enable us to provide you with quality products and services that help you meet your financial needs and objectives.  
  
Security of personal information:  
| The security of personal information about you is our priority. We protect this information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law. We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of personal information they receive.  
---  
As a Citi customer, you have the choice to be taken off our mailing lists for marketing and promotional offers. Should you choose not to receive these materials, you can call our 24-hour CitiPhone Banking number **6225-5225** or login to Citibank Online to fill in the privacy form in the Application Centre.  
Information about cookies  
Cookies facilitate certain features that can make the surfing experience more convenient and valuable for Web users.  
A "cookie" is a small piece of information which a web server can store on your web browser. This is useful for having your browser remember some specific information which the web server can later retrieve. As you browse the web, some cookies are "set" on your Web browser. When you quit your browser, some cookies are stored in your computer's memory in a cookie file, while some expire, or disappear. All cookies have expiration dates. The cookie is set on a particular browser on a particular computer, so when you use a different computer, the cookie will not exist.   
**How We Use Cookies**  
We use cookies for a number of purposes - for example, to maintain continuity during a user session, to gather data about the usage of our website for research and other purposes, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information and marketing offers, or to store a username or encrypted customer identification number so that you do not have to provide this information every time you return to our site. Our cookies will track only your online activity on our website. They will not track your other Internet activity. Cookies set by us cannot be read by and are not shared with any non-Citi website, although we may share some of the cookie information we gather with other Citi companies. Our cookies typically do not gather personally identifiable information. However, if you agree, we may combine our cookie data with personally identifiable information that you provide to us (such as your email address) so that you may receive marketing offers specifically suited to your needs.   
**Cookie Filters**  
You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use some of our online services or website features.   
**Cookies of Other Companies**  
We occasionally use other companies to set cookies on our websites and gather cookie information for us. In some cases we will also use another company to operate web servers for our sites. We use the cookie information gathered by these companies in the same manner as stated in the previous section. The companies we use may not use these cookies for their own internal purposes or share the information gathered with anyone other than Citibank, in accordance with the terms of the contracts they have signed with us.   
For further information regarding cookies of other companies associated with Citibank.com.sg please refer to www.netratings.com.   
**Ordering Online**  
Online ordering systems can use cookies that remember what a person wants to buy. Cookies enable users to keep browsing and adding to their "shopping cart". They can even end a browser session, come back, and still have the same items in their cart from the last session, if they choose to.   
**Registering Online**  
If you decide to register for an informational site, such as a newspaper, periodical or an interest group site, or even a chat group or on-line community, so that you can use it on a regular basis, you will likely be asked to supply some information about yourself. Often cookies are used so that you do not have to identify yourself every time you re-enter the site.   
**Site Personalization**  
Cookies allow users to indicate what types of information they are interested in receiving when they visit a particular site. Users can then view only what they are interested in and not waste time with news or information of no interest to them.  
**Web Site Tracking**  
Tracking allows site owners to find out what pages visitors link to, and interpret or infer what is interesting to them. This helps the owners of sites to keep their content fresh and relevant.   
**Targeted Marketing**  
Cookies can be used to build a profile of where on a particular site you visit. This information is then used to target advertising that might be of interest to you. Some sites use cookies to "remember" which advertisements were sent to you, so that you do not see the same ones again.   
**Security**  
Cookies cannot be used to obtain data from your hard drive, get your e-mail address or steal sensitive or personal information about you. The only way that any private information could be part of your cookie file would be if you personally gave that information to a Web server. Also, each cookie can only be read by the server that set it, so strange servers cannot view or steal the information in a cookie that you have previously accepted.  
Note also that computer viruses are not passed through the setting or use of cookies.   
If you, as a visitor, want to disallow cookies you can do so on your Web browser.
